Guide to the Lester R. Armstrong Photographs circa 1917-1957
Whitman College and Northwest Archives
- Miscellaneous negatives: Old: Trains: Two railroad bed bridges, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1060.07)
- Miscellaneous negatives: Old: View of Walla Walla from top of building, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1060.09)
- Miscellaneous negatives: Old: Walla Walla Parade, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1060.02)
- Miscellaneous people, Undated (Box 6, Folder 32)
- [Miscellaneous photographs], Undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Miscellaneous: 35 mm, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1811)
- Miscellaneous: Business: Houses, Undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Miscellaneous: Commercial, Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous: Missions, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1063)
- Miscellaneous: Negative of block print: The Wagon Wheel room, Marcus Whitman Hotel, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1812)
- Miscellaneous: People and Groups, Undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous: Portraits for practice, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1061)
- Miscellaneous: Residence: Personal, Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous: Steer riding: Rain shed scene: [Little person] (don't fence me in), Undated (Box 3, Folder 1062)
- Miss Piper, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1228)
- Missouri River Landscape, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1064)
- Mitchell, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1065)
- Mitchell: Betty, 1944 July (Box 3, Folder 1066)
- Molette, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1067)
- Molette, Shirley, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1068)
- Molette, Shirley, 1949 February 2 (Box 3, Folder 1069)
- Monkey calendar, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1070)
- Monuments, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1071)
- Moore, Luther: Combine Harvesting, Undated (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Moore, Tommy and Dick, 1953 June 13 (Box 3, Folder 1072)
- Morrison, Harvester Company, 1949 March 29 (Box 3, Folder 1073)
- Motorcycle race, 1949 May 30 (Box 3, Folder 1074)
- Mount Rainier, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1796)
- Mountain from Russell Creek, 1940 November 3 (Box 3, Folder 1084)
- Mountain: View from Bryant Avenue, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1086)
- Mountains: Castle Craig's: California, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1088)
- Mountains: Foothills, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1089)
- Mountains: Grand Tetons: Wyoming, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1091)
- Mountains: Grand Tetons: Wyoming, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1099)
- Mountains: Top of Cabbage hill: Pendleton, Oregon, 1940 October 20 (Box 3, Folder 1090)
- Mountains: View from mountain, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1087)
- Mrs. Lester Smith, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1819)
- Mt. Hood, Circa 1952 (Box 3, Folder 1076)
- Mt. Hood, Circa 1949 (Box 3, Folder 1077)
- Mt. Hood, Circa 1952 (Box 3, Folder 1078)
- Mt. Rainier, Circa 1952 (Box 3, Folder 1079)
- Mt. Rainier, 1946 September (Box 3, Folder 1080)
- Mt. Rainier, Circa 1952 (Box 3, Folder 1081)
- Mt. Rainier, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1082)
- Mt. Rainier, 1949 July 31 (Box 3, Folder 1083)
- Mt. Rainier, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1085)
- Mugs, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1092)
- Mule, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1093)
- Muncey, 1949 November 17 (Box 3, Folder 1094)
- Muncey, Patty, 1947 November 28 (Box 3, Folder 1096)
- Muncy, 1949 November 25 (Box 3, Folder 1095)
- Munsey, Patty, 1947 November 11 (Box 3, Folder 1097)
- Murphy, Mary, 1953 December 3 (Box 3, Folder 1098)
- Musgrove, 1948 March 23 (Box 3, Folder 1100)
- Myron, Doris: Stanfield, Oregon, 1944 May (Box 3, Folder 1101)
- Nash: 12 and Pine: Home Interior, 1945 December 10 (Box 3, Folder 1102)
- National Guard: Air militia: Walla Walla, 1950 June 18 (Box 3, Folder 1104)
- Navy wives: Port Angeles: Gorski, Margie and Elaine Wallgreen, 1951 September 19 (Box 3, Folder 1105)
- Neighbors: Daggets, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1109)
- Neimi, Alice: Horse, 1946 August 21 (Box 3, Folder 1110)
- Nellman, Sergeant: McCaw, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1111)
- Nest: Bird: Killdeer, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1113)
- Nest: Bird: Robin, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1112)
- New Highway: Walla Walla to Milton, 1948 April 26 (Box 2, Folder 722)
- Newquist, Donna, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1114)
- Newton, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1115)
- Night shot: Main street, 1940 October 3 (Box 3, Folder 1116)
- Night shots, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1117)
- [Nine Mile Ranch], 1948 March 3 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Non Commissioned Officer Club: McCaw: St. Patrick, 1945 March 17 (Box 3, Folder 1106)
- Non Commissioned Officer: McCaw Hospital: New years eve, Circa 1945 (Box 3, Folder 1107)
- Non Commissioned Officer: McCaw Hospital: New years party, Circa 1944 (Box 3, Folder 1108)
- O'Rourke, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1134)
- Observatory, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1118)
- Obsidian flow: Near Eastlake, Oregon, 1952 August (Box 3, Folder 1119)
- Odd Fellows, Circa 1948 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Odd Fellows Hall: Walla Walla, Circa 1946 (Box 3, Folder 1120)
- Odd Fellows: Anderson, Oliver: Newly elected Grand Master of Walla Walla: R.R. Hanich, past Grand Master, 1948 June 23 (Box 3, Folder 1122)
- Odd Fellows: Rebecca: Convention, 1948 June 23 (Box 3, Folder 1121)
- Ogle: Identification picture, 1950 July 2 (Box 3, Folder 1123)
- Oliver, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1125)
- Oliver, B.B., Circa 1947 (Box 7, Folder 48)
- Oliver: 50 year anniversary, 1947 September 24 (Box 3, Folder 1124)
- Olympia, Washington, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1126)
- Olympic Penninsula, Circa 1951 (Box 7, Folder 56)
- Onions, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1127)
- Onstot, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1128)
- Onstot: Little girl, 1946 January 5 (Box 3, Folder 1129)
- Ophir, Oregon: Ocean waves, Circa 1952 (Box 3, Folder 1130)
- Orchestra: Charles, King and Virginia Jackson: Armory, 1944 December (Box 3, Folder 1131)
- Orchestra: Hill, Tina: Leader: Armory, 1945 January 13 (Box 3, Folder 1132)
- Oregon City, Oregon, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1133)
- Oster: Copy, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1135)
- Owsley, Bob, 1944 May 4 (Box 3, Folder 1136)
- Ozette, Lake, Circa 1949 (Box 3, Folder 1137)
- PAC co-op meeting: Marcus Whitman Hotel, 1949 October 24 (Box 3, Folder 1140)
- PAC co-op: Burroughs, Emmitt, 1949 October 15 (Box 3, Folder 1139)
- PAC co-op: Williamson, H.P.: Baby, 1949 November 9 (Box 3, Folder 1138)
- Pacific Co-op on Dudey Ranch, Circa 1948 (Box 2, Folder 438)
- Pacific Telephone and Telegraph, 1946 September 6 (Box 3, Folder 1150)
- Pacific Telephone and Telegraph, 1946 September 24 (Box 3, Folder 1151)
- Pacific Telephone and Telegraph, 1946 October 2 (Box 3, Folder 1152)
- Pacific Telephone and Telegraph, 1948 February 20 (Box 3, Folder 1155)
- Pacific Telephone and Telegraph, 1946 September 28 (Box 3, Folder 1160)
- Pacific Telephone and Telegraph, 1946 October 29 (Box 3, Folder 1162)
- Pacific Telephone and Telegraph, 1946 October 23 (Box 3, Folder 1163)
- Pacific Telephone and Telegraph: Board, 1946 January 8 (Box 3, Folder 1141)
- Pacific Telephone and Telegraph: Business Conference: Marcus Whitman, 1948 January 22 (Box 3, Folder 1142)
- Pacific Telephone and Telegraph: Cable Lay, 1947 January 27 (Box 3, Folder 1149)
- Pacific Telephone and Telegraph: Charm class party, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1143)
- Pacific Telephone and Telegraph: Christmas party, 1947 December 22 (Box 3, Folder 1167)
- Pacific Telephone and Telegraph: Christmas party, 1948 December 21 (Box 3, Folder 1168)
- Pacific Telephone and Telegraph: Christmas party, 1946 December 16 (Box 3, Folder 1169)
- Pacific Telephone and Telegraph: Conference: Marcus Whitman, 1948 January 27 (Box 3, Folder 1144)
- Pacific Telephone and Telegraph: Dance, 1947 February 2 (Box 3, Folder 1145)
- Pacific Telephone and Telegraph: Design for living party, 1948 January 7 (Box 3, Folder 1146)
- Pacific Telephone and Telegraph: Eureka, 1946 November 18 (Box 3, Folder 1147)
- Pacific Telephone and Telegraph: Farewell party, 1949 February 11 (Box 3, Folder 1148)
- Pacific Telephone and Telegraph: Open house, 1946 November 13 (Box 3, Folder 1153)
- Pacific Telephone and Telegraph: Operator Business Conference: Marcus Whitman, 1948 January 19 (Box 3, Folder 1154)
- Pacific Telephone and Telegraph: Picture Presentation and Charm City, 1948 December 8 (Box 3, Folder 1156)
- Pacific Telephone and Telegraph: Pin presentation party, 1949 April 26 (Box 3, Folder 1157)
- Pacific Telephone and Telegraph: Retirement party for John Hill, 1950 June 23 (Box 3, Folder 1158)
- Pacific Telephone and Telegraph: St. Patricks party, 1947 March 18 (Box 3, Folder 1159)
- Pacific Telephone and Telegraph: Switchboard, 1948 December (Box 3, Folder 1161)
- Pacific Telephone and Telegraph: Twenty year anniversary party, 1947 November 24 (Box 3, Folder 1164)
- Pacific Telephone and Telegraph: Valentine party, 1949 February 14 (Box 3, Folder 1165)
- Pacific Telephone and Telegraph: Walla Walla County Fair, Circa 1947 (Box 3, Folder 1166)
- Pacific Telephone and Telephone, Circa 1950 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Pacific Telephone and Telephone: Eureka: Cablelay: Banquet, Undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Palouse Falls and Lyons Ferry, Circa 1954 (Box 3, Folder 1170)
- Panorama of Emmitt, Idaho, Circa 1948 (Box 3, Folder 1171)
- Paper drive, 1949 July 27 (Box 3, Folder 1173)
- Paper drive: Last day of war, 1945 August 15 (Box 3, Folder 1172)
- Parade: American legion, 1941 November (Box 3, Folder 1175)
- Parade: Armistice day, Circa 1940 (Box 3, Folder 1176)
- Parade: Dayton, 1942 May (Box 3, Folder 1177)
- Parade: Fair, Circa 1941 (Box 3, Folder 1178)
- Parade: Walla Walla, Circa 1940 (Box 3, Folder 1174)
- Parade: Walla Walla County Fair, 1953 September (Box 3, Folder 1179)
- Parade: Walla Walla Fair, Circa 1941 (Box 3, Folder 1180)
- Parade: Walla Walla Fair, Circa 1940 (Box 3, Folder 1181)
- Parade: Walla Walla Fair, Circa 1939 (Box 3, Folder 1182)
- Park, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1183)
- Park: City: Snow scene, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1185)
- Park: City: Winter scenes, 1945 December 18 (Box 3, Folder 1184)
- Park: Lake, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1186)
- Park: Lake, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1187)
- Park: Mountains Glacier National Park, Circa 1948 (Box 3, Folder 1188)
- Park: Short Sands State Park, 1952 August (Box 3, Folder 1189)
- Park: Spokane, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1190)
- Park: Yellowstone National Park, Circa 1948 (Box 3, Folder 1191)
- Parrish, Toots: Davenport, 1947 July 27 (Box 3, Folder 1192)
- Party: Farewell: Airbase: Prospect Point grange, 1946 February 3 (Box 3, Folder 1193)
- Party: Heimbigner, Bud, 1944 June 25 (Box 3, Folder 1194)
- Pattison, Shirley, Circa 1943 (Box 3, Folder 1195)
- Pattison, Shirley, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1196)
- Pauly: Mail carrier, 1950 January (Box 3, Folder 1197)
- Pea Festival: Milton-Freewater, Circa 1949 (Box 3, Folder 1198)
- Pea Festival: Milton-Freewater, Circa 1950 (Box 3, Folder 1199)
- Pea Festival: Milton-Freewater, 1947 May 10 (Box 3, Folder 1200)
- Pea harvest: Ray Farm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1201)
- Peck, Sam, 1947 September 16 (Box 3, Folder 1202)
- Pennell: Grand champion steer: Prescott, 1948 May 9 (Box 3, Folder 1203)
- Pepsi Cola, 1946 August 16 (Box 3, Folder 1204)
- Pepsi Cola Sky Wrighters, Circa 1946 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Perkins, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1205)
- Perryman, Spencer: Baby, 1950 March 19 (Box 4, Folder 1209)
- Perryman, Tigh, 1948 October 2 (Box 4, Folder 1207)
- Perryman, Tigh and Margaret, 1949 April 23 (Box 4, Folder 1208)
- Perryman: Neighbor, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1206)
- Pershall: Cashier at Roxy, Circa 1949 (Box 4, Folder 1210)
- Peterson's rock garden, Circa 1952 (Box 4, Folder 1211)
- Petrified Log, Vantage, 1940 July (Box 3, Folder 939)
- Petroglyphs, on snow, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1212)
- PFC: Bonner, Luther, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1529)
- Pfeifer, Rose Marie: At seaside, 1947 August (Box 4, Folder 1213)
- Pharmacist, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1214)
- Pharmacist: Krouse: Tallmans Drug, 1944 July (Box 4, Folder 1215)
- Phi Mu, Undated (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Piano: Upholstered, 1950 June 24 (Box 4, Folder 1216)
- Pickets, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1217)
- Picnic: United States Veterans Hospital Employees, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1218)
- Piersol, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1220)
- Pigs: Sucklings at Reser, 1944 March (Box 4, Folder 1219)
- Pikes Peak, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1222)
- Pikes Peak: From Abbott Road, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1223)
- Pikes Peak: From end of School Avenue, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1221)
- Piland, Joan: Rose Marie Crown, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1224)
- Pinza, Emilio: Horses, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1225)
- Pioneer Press: Black and White Print: 5 x 7, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1226)
- Pitzer, Jeanne: Book Nook, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1229)
- Plane Carpenters: Pritz, Robert, Undated (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Plane model, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1230)
- Plumbing, 1941 March 18 (Box 4, Folder 1231)
- Poker, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1232)
- Pollard, Mrs. R.N.: Lewis and Clark Park, 1946 July 14 (Box 4, Folder 1233)
- Pollard, Mrs. R.N.: Lewis and Clark Park, 1946 July 14 (Box 4, Folder 1234)
- Pollard, R.N.: Family Group, Circa 1946 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Polled Hereford show: Walla Walla, Washington, 1948 March 1 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Pope, Doctor and Mrs., 1948 November 19 (Box 4, Folder 1235)
- Pope, Edith: Miss Pope, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1236)
- Pope, Gordon: Wishing well, 1947 May (Box 4, Folder 1237)
- Pope, Phillip: Biological charts, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1238)
- Port Angeles, Washington, Circa 1951 (Box 7, Folder 58)
- Port Angeles: Docks and Boats, Undated (Box 2, Folder 425)
- Port Kelley, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1239)
- Port Kelly, Loading Barge, Undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Portland: Street scene, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1240)
- Portland: Street scene, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1241)
- Portland: Zoo, Circa 1954 (Box 4, Folder 1242)
- Portraits, Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Post office employees, 1948 June 29 (Box 4, Folder 1243)
- Postal Employees, Circa 1948 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Potter, 1945 February 20 (Box 4, Folder 1244)
- Potter, 1945 March (Box 4, Folder 1246)
- Power plant, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1247)
- Powers, John: Daughter, high school grad: Starbuck, Washington, 1957 February 26 (Box 4, Folder 1248)
- Priest Lake, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1249)
- Printed matter: Correspondence, Undated (Box 6, Folder 43)
- Printer: Ferney, Mr. Jesse, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1250)
- Prisoners of war: Germans: World War II, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1258)
- Pritz, Robert, 1948 February 22 (Box 4, Folder 1251)
- Proctor, Lorn D.: Loading tanks at Walla Walla Airfield, 1948 January 28 (Box 4, Folder 1252)
- Puget Sound, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1253)
- Pulliam, M.L., 1948 November 24 (Box 4, Folder 1254)
- Puppies, Circa 1949 (Box 4, Folder 1255)
- Puppies, 1948 December 19 (Box 4, Folder 1256)
- Pussy willows, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1257)
- Puyallup State Fair, Washington, Circa 1951 (Box 7, Folder 53)
- Quinn, R.A.: Bergevin barn, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1259)
- Racing horse, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1260)
- Radio broadcasting, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1261)
- Railroad, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1262)
- Railroad car, french: Salem, Oregon, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1263)
- Railroad engine: Off of track, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1264)
- Railroad: Old timers: R.R, 44026 (Box 4, Folder 1265)
- Ranch, Stock: Henry and Dora Johnson, 1951 September (Box 4, Folder 1266)
- Ranches, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1267)
- Random shots: Near Book Nook, 1952 May 31 (Box 3, Folder 1058)
- Ranger station: Bungalow, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1268)
- Ransom, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1269)
- Ray Dean, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1270)
- Ray, Mrs. Gene, 1949 October 23 (Box 4, Folder 1271)
- Red Cross: Station at Freedom, 1948 March 29 (Box 4, Folder 1272)
- Red star, 1950 July 21 (Box 4, Folder 1274)
- Red star: Elk contest, 1949 November 20 (Box 4, Folder 1273)
- Redding, California, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1275)
- Redwoods, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1277)
- Redwoods, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1278)
- Reece, Lieutenant: Wedding, 1945 December 2 (Box 4, Folder 1279)
- Reihl, J, 1946 July (Box 4, Folder 1280)
- Reil, 1946 July 6 (Box 4, Folder 1281)
- Releases: Armstrong, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1783)
- Reo star, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1276)
- Residence, Interior, Circa 1946 (Box 6, Folder 50)
- Residence: Luther, Burbank: Santa Rosa, California, 1927 June 1927 (Box 4, Folder 1282)
- Resorts, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1283)
- Restaurant, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1284)
- Restaurant: Peeling vegetables, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1285)
- Rice, Tom, 1949 March 25 (Box 4, Folder 1286)
- Richards, Viola: McCaw Hospital, 1944 August (Box 4, Folder 1287)
- River road, Snake, Circa 1949 (Box 4, Folder 1290)
- River, Columbia: Wenatchee, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1289)
- River, Snake: South Idaho, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1291)
- River: Columbia River rocks: Near Wallula, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1288)
- Rivers, Miscellaneous: Old, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1292)
- Road mountain: Kooskooskie, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1293)
- Robanske, Alick: birth certificate, 1942 November 5 (Box 4, Folder 1294)
- Roberts, Mrs., 1951 June 5 (Box 4, Folder 1299)
- Robin and hub cap, 1949 April 22 (Box 4, Folder 1295)
- Robinson, Laura Lee, 1944 March 28 (Box 4, Folder 1296)
- Robinson, Laura Lee, 1944 November 7 (Box 4, Folder 1297)
- Robinson, Lee: Sewing Machine, 1948 November 26 (Box 4, Folder 1298)
- Robinson: Sewing Machine, Undated (Box 6, Folder 44)
- Robinson: Sewing machines, 1948 August 25 (Box 4, Folder 1300)
- Rodeo, Walla Walla, 1945 April 22 (Box 4, Folder 1301)
- Rodeo, Walla Walla, 1945 April 22 (Box 4, Folder 1302)
- Rodeo, Walla Walla, 1945 April 22 (Box 4, Folder 1303)
- Rodeo: Bedford, Cecil: Walla Walla, Circa 1945 (Box 4, Folder 1304)
- Rodeo: Bucking Brahma, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1305)
- Rodeo: Pasco, 1944 May (Box 4, Folder 1306)
- Rodeo: Pasco, 1944 May 28 (Box 4, Folder 1307)
- Rodeo: Stanfield, Oregon, 1944 May (Box 4, Folder 1308)
- Rodeo: Walla Walla, 1945 September 1 (Box 4, Folder 1309)
- Rojas, Judith: Lima, Peru, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1310)
- Romine: Truck at Penitentiary, 1946 July 8 (Box 4, Folder 1311)
- Ronis, Captain, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1312)
- Roots, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1313)
- Roots: Cutting crew, 1948 January 2 (Box 4, Folder 1314)
- Ross, Elizabeth, 1940 December (Box 4, Folder 1315)
- Ross, Miss, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1316)
- Round-up: Pendleton, Circa 1946 (Box 4, Folder 1317)
- Round-up: Walla Walla, 1943 September (Box 4, Folder 1318)
- Rownes, Bee: Orchard in Bloom, 1948 May 7 (Box 4, Folder 1319)
- Rubin, Second Lieutenant Dean: Fort Douglas, Utah, 1942 October 7 (Box 4, Folder 1320)
- Rulo, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1321)
- Rusell, Clay: Grave, 1947 June 8 (Box 4, Folder 1322)
- Rusell, Clay: Group: Veterans of Foreign Wars Convention, 1940 June 1 (Box 4, Folder 1323)
- Russell Creek, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1324)
- Rust, John, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1325)
- Ryder, Carl, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1326)
- Sale: Frazier, Alex: Sold out for United States airport, 1942 March (Box 4, Folder 1329)
- Saltmarsh, Mrs. Nora, 1953 January 10 (Box 4, Folder 1330)
- Salvation Army, Undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Salvation Army: Church, 7th and Poplar Street, 1946 November 27 (Box 4, Folder 1331)
- Salvation Army: Junior soldier class, 1947 January 26 (Box 4, Folder 1332)
- Salvation Army: Scout troop, 1947 March 3 (Box 4, Folder 1334)
- Salvation Army: Taken, 1946 May 11 (Box 4, Folder 1333)
- San Francisco, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1335)
- Sawmill, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1336)
- Sawmill: Pribilski: Walla Walla Washington, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1337)
- Scenery: Burial, local, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1340)
- Scenery: Unidentified, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1798)
- Scenic Sunset, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1341)
- Scenic: Fir trees and clouds, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1338)
- Scenic: From Russell Creek: Blue mountains, 1950 July 10 (Box 4, Folder 1339)
- Schafer, Charles: First Reconn. Soldier: Pendleton Air base, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1342)
- Schafer, Charles: First Reconn. Soldier: Pendleton, Oregon, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1343)
- Schmeltzer: Flower show: Armory hall, Circa 1950 (Box 4, Folder 1344)
- Schmidt, Cleaners, Undated (Box 6, Folder 45)
- Schmidt: Cleaners, 1947 March 28 (Box 4, Folder 1345)
- School: American Legion health class, Circa 1942 (Box 4, Folder 1346)
- School: St. Vincent's music group, Circa 1946 (Box 6, Folder 46)
- Schools: Rulo, Circa 1919 (Box 4, Folder 1347)
- Schroeder, Gus, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1349)
- Schroeder, Gus, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1350)
- Schroeder, Gus, 1957 November 22 (Box 4, Folder 1351)
- Scott, 1941 December (Box 4, Folder 1352)
- Sea Views: Oregon Highway: Coast of Oregon, 1947 August (Box 4, Folder 1361)
- Seals: Depoe Bay, etcetera, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1353)
- Sears, Woodworking window display, 1948 September 25 (Box 4, Folder 1356)
- Sears: Roebuck and company, 1946 March 7 (Box 4, Folder 1354)
- Sears: Roebuck and company: Santa Claus, 1946 December (Box 4, Folder 1355)
- Seascape: Depoe Bay, Circa 1947 (Box 5, Folder 1785)
- Seascape: Depoe Bay, Oregon, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1802)
- Seascape: Fogarty Creek, Oregon, Circa 1949 (Box 5, Folder 1790)
- Seascape: Kalaloch, Washington, Circa 1947 (Box 5, Folder 1786)
- Seascape: Tip of olympic peninsula, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1357)
- Seascapes: Oregon Coast, Circa 1949 (Box 4, Folder 1358)
- Seascapes: Parker residence: Wedderburn, Oregon, 1947 August (Box 4, Folder 1359)
- Seattle, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1360)
- Sekiu, Washington, Circa 1947 (Box 5, Folder 1787)
- Sekiu, Washington, Circa 1951 (Box 7, Folder 57)
- Sewer, Division Street, Circa 1948 (Box 4, Folder 1363)
- Sewer: Construction at South Division Street, 1951 April 16 (Box 4, Folder 1362)
- Sewer: Plugged, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1364)
- Sheep, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1365)
- Sheep, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1366)
- Sheep on Columbia River: Shearing station, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1367)
- Sheep shearing, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1368)
- Sheep: Maiboch, Ted, 1947 March 2 (Box 5, Folder 1784)
- Shingle mill: Port Angeles, 1951 September (Box 4, Folder 1369)
- Shirley, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1370)
- Shore Acres State Park, Oregon, Circa 1952 (Box 4, Folder 1371)
- Shriners: Car given to masons: Spokane Shriners unit of crippled children, 1951 February 25 (Box 4, Folder 1348)
- Sidewalk and tree, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1372)
- Sign shop, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1373)
- Signs, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1374)
- Signs: Board, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1375)
- Signs: Bulletin, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1376)
- Signs: Card, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1377)
- Signs: Christmas, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1390)
- Signs: Cloth, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1378)
- Signs: Coca Cola, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1379)
- Signs: Glass, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1380)
- Signs: Metal, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1381)
- Signs: Neon, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1382)
- Signs: Oil Company, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1383)
- Signs: Process, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1384)
- Signs: Traffic, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1385)
- Signs: Truck, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1386)
- Signs: Trucks, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1387)
- Signs: Trucks, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1388)
- Signs: Wall, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1389)
- Siverling, John L.: Shorthorn Bull, Circa 1947 (Box 6, Folder 47)
- Siverling, Shorthorn, Circa 1947 (Box 4, Folder 1391)
- Skating, roller, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1392)
- Skating, roller, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1393)
- Skating, roller: Walla Walla, Circa 1952 (Box 4, Folder 1394)
- Skeletons: Exposition building: Los Angeles, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1395)
- Skiing, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1396)
- Slavenburg and Cummings: Veterans of Foreign Wars, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1397)
- Smelt, Swimming, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1788)
- Smelter, Anaconda, Montana, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1398)
- Smelts, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1399)
- Smeltzer, Mrs., 1946 April 28 (Box 4, Folder 1400)
- Smith, Barbara, 1945 March 21 (Box 4, Folder 1401)
- Smith, Betty: Child, 1957 March 26 (Box 4, Folder 1402)
- Smith, Betty: Susie, 1951 April 26 (Box 4, Folder 1403)
- Smithson, Dr. Carl B.: Diplomas 1,2,3,4,5, 1946 February 20 (Box 5, Folder 1404)
- Smithson, Lieutenant Col., 1946 February 21 (Box 4, Folder 1405)
- Smoke, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1406)
- Smoking Stand, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1407)
- Smut, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1408)
- Snake, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1409)